(Penny:)Why'd you get that?
You hate lamb.
(Sheldon:)I was asking for directions.
(Sheldon:)Apparently, there was
a communication problem.
(Leonard:)I thought Amy was gonna drive
you home.
(Sheldon:)I thought so, too,
but she's acting very strangely.
(Sheldon:)I was discussing it with a Sri Lankan
fellow on the bus,
(Sheldon:)and he hypothesized that a tiger may
have recently run across her shadow.
(Sheldon:)Although he may have just been trying
to drum up business
(Sheldon:)for his brother-in-law's
witch doctor practice.
(Penny:)Okay, Sheldon,
what happened between you and Amy?
(Sheldon:)Well, can you believe she said
I embarrassed her?
(Sheldon:)Yeah.
(Sheldon:)But you didn't even hear the details.
(Penny:)Sheldon...
(Leonard:)I've known you a long time,
and I'm going to tell you this
(Leonard:)with all the love
I can possibly muster.
(Leonard:)Amy's right. You're wrong.